{
    "id": "208fa7306a2a4a189ebbf52ac1b266a4",
    "title": "Infinitive Or Gerund",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They made the child …………………………. the milk.",
            "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "to drink",
                "drinking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They forced me ……………………………… the papers.",
            "description": "Forced is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "sign",
                "to sign",
                "to signing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy was not allowed …………………………….. the exam.",
            "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "to write",
                "from writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They let him ………………………………..",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She prevented him ………………………………….. her room.",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by object + from + ing form",
            "answers": [
                "enter",
                "to enter",
                "from entering"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother encouraged the boy ……………………………. again.",
            "description": "Encourage is followed by object + to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "try",
                "to try",
                "from trying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Children should be discouraged ………………………………..",
            "description": "Discourage is followed by from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to smoke",
                "from smoking",
                "to smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You should stop him ………………………………..",
            "description": "Stop is followed by from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to leave",
                "from leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was permitted ……………………………….. early.",
            "description": "Permitted is followed by to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "to leave",
                "from leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Stringent punishments deter people ……………………………………. crimes.",
            "description": "Deter is followed by object + from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to commit",
                "from committing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion struggled …………………………………… itself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to free",
                "from freeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I remember …………………………………… him as  a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meeting",
                "to meet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}